# **Mohamed Gamal**



## **Contact**

#### Address:

7193 Muhammad Al-Qusaibi Street, King Faisal District, Riyadh, **Saudi Arabia** 

### **Nationality:**

Egyptian

#### BirthDate:

03/6/1998

#### Phone:

0564842804

#### **Email:**

mohamedgamal1455@gmail.com

# Languages

**English** 

## **Hobbies**

- Writing
- Sketching
- Photography
- Design

# **Summary**

I am a highly accomplished computer science graduate from the Higher Institute for computer science and information system in Egypt, consistently ranking first in my class and achieving excellent grades. With two years of experience as a teaching assistant in the Information Systems Department at the Higher Institute for Advanced Studies, I have honed strong interpersonal and communication skills. Currently, I am conducting research at Beni Suef University after completing the pre-Masters stage. I am deeply passionate about computer science and am driven to make significant contributions to any organization I work for.

# **Skill Highlights**

- SQL Server
- Oracle SQL
- MongoDB
- Python
- Flask
- Machine Learning
- Deep Learning

- data analysis
- Java
- C#
- HTML/CSS/JS
- Asp.net Core MVC
- Web Api
- Flutter

# **Experience**

## **BackEnd Developer in company inootec –** 8/2019 to 11/2021

 Designing and developing web services and APIs: I developed robust and scalable web services and APIs using ASP.NET

# Teaching Assistant in Department of Management Information Systems - 10/2020 to 10/2022

• Teaching Assistant in the Department of Management Information Systems responsible for explaining the practical parts of programming materials and databases.

### **Trainer at Abad Training Institute** - 11/2022 to Now

 Training on programming and databases such as C#, asp.net, Python, Oracle and SQI server

## **Education**

- Pre-Master's stage in Computer Science ,Beni Suef University, Egypt
- Bachelor of Science in Management Information Systems, 2020 Higher Institute of Computers and Information Systems, Egypt